Dude, there are so many cool things
we could be doing tonight. Look.
At the Glendale Galleria:
"Put on your best zoot suit.
(Raj:)It's a salute to swing music...
(Raj:)...in the center court near Macy's,
5 p.m. to 9 p.m."
Huh? Huh?
(Raj:)A salute to zoot.
(Raj:)-Sounds like a hoot.
-I'm sorry, Raj.
(Sheldon:)I have no desire
to salute any article of clothing tonight...
(Sheldon:)...much less one that's linked
to race riots in the 1940s.
(Raj:)Race riots?
(Sheldon:)The Zoot Suit Riots.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Raj:)I always thought that was
some sort of after-Christmas sale.
Why don't we go to the galleria
and walk around?
(Sheldon:)I don't need anything at the galleria.
You need anything at the galleria?
(Raj:)No, we would just walk around
and see what's what.
(Sheldon:)That's a semantically null sentence.
(Raj:)Okay, well, how about this?
From the university website:
"Seven p.m. to 10 p.m.,
Norton Hall Multipurpose Room...